<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
 <!--    <string name="hello">Hello World, Gosmore!</string> -->
    <string name="app_name">Gosmore</string>
    <string name="fastest">Fastest Route</string>
    <string name="summary_fastest">Not the shortest</string>
    <string name="north2d">Orient Northwards in 2D</string>
    <string name="summary_north2d">Don\'t use the compass in 2D</string>
    <string name="vehicle">Vehicle</string>
    <string name="summary_vehicle">Vehicle / Transport mode</string>
    <string name="tts">Voice Language</string>
    <string name="summary_tts">Text to Speech instructions</string>
    <string name="routing_progress">Calculating Route</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string> <!-- Routing and no map dialogs -->
    <string name="ok">OK</string> <!-- About and no map dialogs -->
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string name="about_msg">
        Copyright (C) 2011 Nic Roets and Gosmore contributors. All rights reserved.\n
        THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY NIC ROETS ``AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL NIC ROETS OR
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n\n
                
   Some of the icons are copyright (c) 2005-2008, The Android Open Source Project\n

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.\n\n
        
        Some of the data bundled with or downloaded by this application fall
        under the following copyright. When the application interprets this data,
        it does not affects it\'s copyright, only the copyright of the output.\n\n
        Map data (C) OpenStreetMap contributors CC-BY-SA\n
        http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.0/\n\n
        Map styles and icons (C) JOSM and Gosmore contributors under the GNU
        General Public License version 2 or later\n\n
        City names and locations in default map (C)
        Geonames.org contributors CC-BY 3.0\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="no_location_title">No location specified</string>
    <string name="no_location_msg">
    To find your location tap the location button.\n\n
    To find a city, tap the search button and enter the first few letters.</string>
    <string name="first_map_title">Location acquired</string>
    <string name="first_map_msg">Download the map for your area ?</string>
    <string name="no_sdcard_title">No SD Card</string>
    <string name="no_sdcard_msg">The external storage is not mounted.</string>
</resources>
